Thomas Barenghi

Full Stack Developer | Haedo, Buenos Aires - Argentina

linkedin.com/in/thomasbarenghi | github.com/thomasbarenghi | thomasbarenghi@gmail.com | +54 11 6996-1733

Professional Profile

I have been passionate about development since I was 12 years old, when I started my first personal projects. I think software is a great combination of art and engineering. Throughout my career, I worked in multidisciplinary teams, with more than 150 people, collaborating on web and application development projects, always seeking to contribute to the success of each task. I value teamwork, since I believe that the best solutions arise when diverse skills and human talent are combined.

Professional Education

University Technician in Programming

2024 - In progress

National University of Hurlingham

50% completed, with a grade of 9. Training in software design, development and programming, with a practical approach to solve real problems and apply technical knowledge.

Electronics Technician Dec. 2021

E.E.S.T No. 8 of Moron

Training in design, maintenance and repair of analog and digital electronic systems. Experience in testing, measurements and marketing of electronic equipment, with a focus on quality and safety.

Experience

Full Stack Developer

Jun. 2023 - Jan. 2024

Non-Country | Labor practices

Developed scalable web applications, working on both frontend and backend. Used technologies such as React, Node.js and PostgreSQL, collaborating closely with the backend and UX/UI teams to ensure a smooth and efficient integration.

Appliance Repair Technician

Oct. 2021 - Dec. 2022

Cibeles Service

I was responsible for the maintenance and repair of appliances, ensuring compliance with deadlines and optimizing time for each task. I quickly adapted to a dynamic environment, where each situation demanded efficient solutions and flexibility in the face of unforeseen events.

Lidar Image and Video Analyst for Al

May. 2021 - Sep. 2021

Smart Ecosystem Philippines Inc.

During an InHouse program, I gained advanced skills in LiDAR image and video analysis applied to artificial intelligence. I specialized in 2D and 3D LiDAR data processing, and identifying patterns and anomalies. Additionally, I developed the ability to communicate findings clearly and effectively.

Projects

Buffet | UNAHUR Jan. 2024 - Oct. 2024

Public Utility

Web application to improve the experience at the university buffet. It allows you to view the menu, select products, make payments and receive notifications in real time. **Technologies:** NextJS, Typescript, PostgreSQL.

LleGO! | Not Country Apr. 2023 - May. 2023

Internship

Platform to connect local stores with customers and delivery people, similar to Uber Eats or Rappi. Allows you to browse stores, select products and place orders. **Technologies**: NextJS, TailwindCSS, Typescript, NestJS, PostgreSQL.

Skills and Certifications

Programming: Javascript, Typescript, ReactJS, NextJS, SvelteJS, Html, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, ExpressJS, NestJS, WebSockets, Supabase, Arduino, PostgreSQL, SQLite, MongoDB, GraphQL.

Design: Wix, Figma, Wordpress.

- Database Administration Using PostgreSQL. CEDAC India. December 2024.
- English Certificate B1 Intermediate. EF SET. May 2023.
- Full Stack Web Development. Henry Bootcamp. 700 hours of theoretical-practical courses. May 2023.
- Quality management. National University of La Matanza. December 2021.